Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 2-627, OV 868)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Music
    - Waring, Tom
      - Susan Simpson. New York: Sprague-Coleman, 1939., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/5)
    - Warren, Harry and Ralph Blane
      - Spring isn't everything. Hollywood: Four Jays Music Co., 1954. (Box-folder 510/6)
      - The Stanley steamer. Hollywood: Four Jays Music Co., 1954., 2 copies (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Jack Brooks
      - That's amore. New York: Paramount Music Corp., 1953. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Warren, Harry, Lew Brown and Sidney Clare
      - One sweet letter from you. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1927., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Al Dubin
      - Forty second street. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1932. (Box-folder 441/6, 510/6)
      - I only have eyes for you. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1934. (Box-folder 441/6)
      - I've got to sing a torch song. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1933. (Box-folder 510/6)
      - Lullaby of Broadway. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1935., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
      - Lulu's back in town. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1935. (Box-folder 510/6)
      - September in the rain. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Arthur Freed
      - Coffee time. New York: Four Jays Music Co., Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 441/6)
      - The house of singing bamboo. Hollywood: Four Jays Music Co., 1954. (Box-folder 510/6)
      - This heart of mine. New York: Triangle Music Corp., 1943. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Ira Gershwin
      - My one and only highland fling. New York: Four Jays Music Co., Inc., 1948., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
      - The poetry of motion. Hollywood: Four Jays Music Co., 1954., 2 copies (Box-folder 510/6)
      - Week-end in the country. New York: Four Jays Music Co., Inc., 1954. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Mack Gordon
      - Chattanooga choo choo. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1941., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
      - Friendly star. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 510/6)
      - I had the craziest dream. New York: Bregman, Vocco & Conn, Inc., 1942., 2 copies (Box-folder 510/6)
      - If you feel like singing, sing. New York: Four Jays Music Co., Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 441/6)
      - It happened in Sun Valley. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1941., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
      - There will never be another you. New York: Mayfair Music Corp., 1942., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6, 510/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Bud Green
      - I love my baby. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1925., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Warren, Harry and Johnny Mercer
      - It's a great big world. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 441/6, 510/6)
      - Jeepers creepers. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1938. (Box-folder 441/6)
      - On the Atchison, Topeka and the Sante Fe. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Wayne, Bernie and Ben Raleigh
      - Laughing on the outside. New York: Broadcast Music Inc., 1946. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Wayne, Dotty, Richard Loring and Steve Binder
      - Ask me a question. Los Angeles: Romy Music Productions, 1964. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Wayne, Mable and Kim Gannon
      - A dreamer's holiday. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1949., 2 copies (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Wayne, Mabel, Lewis and Young
      - In a little Spanish town. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Wayne, Sid, Joe Sherman and Jackie Kannon
      - Prunes. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1952. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Waxman, Franz
      - Theme from "Peyton Place". New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1958. (Box-folder 441/6)
    - Webster, Paul Francis and Sonny Burke
      - Black coffee. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1948. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Wechter, Cissy and Julius Wechter
      - Spanish flea. Hollywood: Almo Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Weersma, Melle and Hal Hallifax
      - Penny serenade. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weil, Cynthia and Barry Mann
      - Blame it on the bossa nova. New York: Screen Gems - Columbia Music, Inc., 1962. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Weill, Kurt
      - Mack the knife. New York: Harms Inc., 1928. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Weill, Kurt and Maxwell Andersen
      - September song. New York: DeSylva, Brown & Henderson, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weill, Kurt and Ira Gershwin
      - Lady in the dark. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1941. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weill, Kurt and Alan Jay Lerner
      - Here I'll stay. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1948. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Weinberg, Mortimer, Charley Marks and Harry Warren
      - Where do you work-a-John?. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1926., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weiss, Doris M.
      - My merry little Christmas tree. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weiss, Stephan and Bernie Baum
      - Music! music! music!. New York: Cromwell Music, Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Welk, Lawrence and Norman Lee
      - Champagne polka. New York: Peer International Corp., 1945. (Box-folder 510/6)
    - Wells, Jack, Alfred Bryan and Willie Weston
      - Joan of Arc they are calling you. New York: Waterson, Berlin & Snyder Co., 1917. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Wendling, Pete, George W. Meyer and Sam M. Lewis
      - I believe in miracles. New York: Cromwell Music, Inc., 1962. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Wenrich, Percy and Edward Madden
      - Moonlight bay. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1912. (Box-folder 442/1, 510/7)
    - Wenrich, Percy and Jack Mahoney
      - When you wore a tulip. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1914. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Wenrich, Percy and Harry Tobias
      - Chimes of Arcady. New York: Tobey Music Corp., 1958. (Box-folder 510/7)
      - Sail along, silv'ry moon. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1942. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - West, Eugene, James McCaffrey and Dave Ringle
      - Roll on, Mississippi roll on. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1931., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/1)
    - West, Red
      - If every day was like Christmas. New York: Atlantic Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Wester, Harry and George Dodson
      - Gay fiesta. Lake Mary: Dodson & Wester Music Pub., 1966. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Westmoreland, Paul
      - Detour. New York: Hill and Range Songs, Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weston, Harris, Bert Lee and Irving Taylor
      - Knees bent up Mother Brown. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1939. (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weston, Paul
      - The Hasegawa general store. New York: Hanover Music Corp., 1964., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weston, Paul, Alan Bergman and Marilyn Keith
      - Christmas is the season of the bells. Pacific Palisades: Hanover Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 510/7)
      - Goodbye is a lonesome sound. New York: Empress Music Inc., 1961. (Box-folder 442/1)
      - Merry Christmas. Pacific Palisades: Hanover Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Weston, Paul and Sol. Meyer
      - Tweet and toot. New York: Hanover Music Corp., 1953., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/1)
    - Weyand, Mayruth
      - Grandma's comin' for Christmas. New York: Plainview Music, Inc., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/1)
    - White, Pat
      - It's the same old Shillelagh. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Whiting, Richard A., Nacio Herb Brown and B .G. DeSylva
      - Eadie was a lady. New York: Harms Inc., 1932. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Whiting, Richard A., Newell Chase and Leo Robin
      - My ideal. New York: Famous Music Corp., 1930. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Whiting, Richard A. and Raymond B. Egan
      - The Japanese sandman. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1920. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Whiting, Richard A., Gus Kahn and Raymond B. Egan
      - Ain't we got fun. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1921. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Whiting, Richard A. and Johnny Mercer
      - Hooray for Hollywood: New York: Harms Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Whiting, Richard A. and Leo Robin
      - Louise. New York: Famous Music Corp., 1929. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Whitney, Joan and Alex Kramer
      - Ain't nobody here but us chickens. New York: Sun Music Co., 1947., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
      - High on a windy hill. New York: Broadcast Music Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 510/7)
      - There's always an extra potato. New York: Kramer-Whitney, Inc., 1965., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Whitney, Joan, Alex Kramer and Hy Zaret
      - Christmas roses. New York: Dartmouth Music, Inc., 1952. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Whitter, Henry, Charles W. Noell and Fred J. Lewey
      - The wreck of old 97. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1924., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Wilder, Alec and Marshall Barer
      - Summer is a-comin' in. New York: Essex Music, Inc., 1952., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Wilder, Alec, Morty Palitz and Bill Engvick
      - While we're young. New York: Regent Music Corp., 1943. (Box-folder 442/2, 510/7)
    - Williams, Clarence
      - Ugly Chile. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1917., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Clarence and Lucy Fletcher
      - Sugar blues. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1919. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Clarence and Spencer Williams
      - Royal garden blues. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1919., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Curley
      - Half as much. Nashville: Acuff-Rose Pub., 1951. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Curley and Billy Simmons
      - Mississippi. Nashville: Acuff-Rose Pub., 1950. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Hugh and Jimmy Kennedy
      - Red sails in the sunset. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1935., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Johnny
      - Checkmate. Universal City: Hawaii Music Co., 1960. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Williams, Johnny and Johnny Mercer
      - A big beautiful ball. New York: Harms, Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Mary Lou, William Johnson and Snub Mosley
      - Pretty eyed baby. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1947. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Williams, Spencer
      - She'll be comin' 'round the mountain. New York: Joe Davis, Inc., 1930. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Williams, Spencer and Clarence Williams
      - I ain't gonna give nobody none o' this jelly roll. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1919., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Willis, Virgil
      - I've got a secret with Santa Claus. Houston: Cleve Pub. Co., 1965. (Box-folder 442/2)
    - Wills, Johnnie Lee and Deacon Andersen
      - Rag mop. New York: Hill and Range Songs, Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Willson, Meredith
      - Arm in arm. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Belly up to the bar, boys. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1960. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - The big clown balloons. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Chick-a-pen. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1960. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Dear Mister Santa Claus. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Expect things to happen. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - George. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1946. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - He's my friend. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Here comes the springtime. New York: Plymouth Music Co., 1951. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Here's love. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - I ain't down yet. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1960., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - I see the moon. New York: Plymouth Music Co., 1953. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - I'll never say no. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1960. (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Love, come take me again. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - My state, my Kansas, my home. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1961., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - My wish. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - The peony bush. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1949. (Box-folder 442/3, 510/7)
      - Pine cones and holly berries. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Seventy six trombones. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1957. (Box-folder 510/7)
      - That man over there. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/3)
      - The unsinkable Molly Brown-vocal selections. New York: Frank Music Corp. and Rinimer Corp., 1961. (Box-folder 442/3)
    - Wilson, Brian
      - Be true to your school. Hawthorne: Sea of Tunes Pub., Co., 1963. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wiseman, Scott
      - Have I told you lately that I love you?. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1945. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wittstatt, Hans and Dory Langdon
      - Pepe. New York: Ed. Kassner & Co., 1957., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wolcott, Charles, Ed. Penner and T. Hee
      - The reluctant dragon. New York: Broadcast Music Inc., 1941. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Wolf, Tommy and Fran Landesman
      - Apples on the lilac tree. Wolfe-Mills Music Inc., 1957. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wood, Guy and Sammy Gallop
      - Shoo-fly pie and apple pan dowdy. New York: Capitol Songs, Inc., 1946. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Wood, Leo
      - Somebody stole my gal. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1918. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Woods, Harry
      - Paddlin' Madelin' home. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1925., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Side by side. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1927., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Woods, Harry and Mort Dixon
      - I'm looking for a four leaf clover. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1927. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - River, stay 'way from my door. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1931., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Woods, Harry and Arthur Freed
      - Here comes the sun. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1930. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Woods, Harry, Billy Rose and Mort Dixon
      - I wishn't I was in Peoria. New York: Bourne, Inc., 1925., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Woods, Harry, Charles Tobias and Al Sherman
      - Me too. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1926., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wooley, Sheb
      - The purple people eater. Hollywood: Cordial Music Co., 1958. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Worth, Bobby and Henry Sanicola
      - I'm coming home, Los Angeles. New York: Sands Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Worth, Maynard
      - Whoopee ti yi yo. New York: Broadcast Music Inc., 1941. (Box-folder 510/7)
    - Wright, Robert and George Forrest
      - Anya. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1964. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Chime in!. New York: Empress Music Inc., 1961., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Drawn to you. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Hand in hand. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1964. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Here tonight, tomorrow where?. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - If this is goodbye. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - It's the same. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1952., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Little hands. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Night of my nights. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1953. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Now is my moment. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Snowflakes and sweethearts. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - This is my kind of love. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wrubel, Allie and Mort Dixon
      - The lady in red. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1935. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wrubel, Allie and Herb Magidson
      - How long has this been going on?. New York: DeSylva, Brown & Henderson, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 442/4)
      - I can't love you any more. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1940. (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Wyche, Sid and Mayme Watts
      - Alright, okay! you win. New York: Melody Lane Pub., Inc., 1955., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/4)
    - Xanrof, L.
      - Le fiacre. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1945. (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Yanguas, Mariano
      - Caminitos. Madrid: Mariono Yanguas-Dr. Esquerdo, 1936. (Box-folder 510/8)
    - Yellen, Jack and Milton Ager
      - Don't put a tax on the beautiful girls. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1919. (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Youmans, Vincent and Irving Caesar
      - Sometimes I'm happy. New York: Harms, Inc., 1927. (Box-folder 510/8)
      - Tea for two. New York: Harms Inc., 1924. (Box-folder 510/8)
    - Youmans, Vincent and Anne Caldwell
      - I know that you know. New York: Harms Inc., 1926. (Box-folder 510/8)
    - Youmans, Vincent and Edward Heyman
      - Drums in my heart. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1931. (Box-folder 510/8)
    - Youmans, Vincent, Gus Kahn and Edward Eliscu
      - Carioca. New York: T.B. Harms, Inc., 1933. (Box-folder 442/5)
      - Flying down to Rio. New York: T.B. Harms, Inc., 1933. (Box-folder 442/5)
      - Music makes me. New York: T.B. Harms, Inc., 1933. (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Youmans, Vincent, William Rose and Edward Eliscu
      - Great day. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1929. (Box-folder 442/5, 510/8)
      - More than you know. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1929. (Box-folder 442/5, 510/8)
    - Young, Victor
      - Red rosey bush. New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 442/5, 510/8)
    - Young, Victor and Harold Adamson
      - Around the world. Beverly Hills: Victor Young Pub., 1956. (Box-folder 442/5, 510/8)
    - Young, Victor and Sammy Cahn
      - Written on the wind. New York: Keys Music Inc., 1956. (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Young, Victor and Will J. Harris
      - Sweet Sue - just you. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1928., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Young, Victor and Edward Heyman
      - Love letters. (Box-folder 510/8)
    - Young, Victor and Bob Hilliard
      - All American rainbow. New York: Alamo Music, Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 442/5)
      - Lord, you made the night too long. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1932., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Young, Victor and Ned Washington
      - My foolish heart. New York: Santly-Joy, Inc., 1949. (Box-folder 510/8)
      - Stella by starlight. New York: Famous Music Corp., 1946. (Box-folder 510/8)
    - Yradier, Sebastian
      - La paloma (The dove). New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1942. (Box-folder 442/5)
    - Zabka, Stan and Don Upton
      - Christmas eve in my home town. New York: Broadcast Music Inc., 1951., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/6)
    - Zaret, Hy and Lou Singer
      - One meat ball. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1944., 2 copies (Box-folder 442/6)
    - Zaritzky, Bernard
      - The little white duck. New York: General Music Pub. Co. Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 510/9)
    - Zimmerman, Charles A.
      - Anchors aweigh. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1907., 2 copies (Box-folder 510/9)
    - Foreign (Japanese)
      - The five pennies. (Box-folder 510/10)
      - One way ticket. (Box-folder 510/10)
- Scripts (Box 628-686)
  - The Danny Kaye Show, 1963-1967
    Television scripts, including the original embossed leather binders.
    Arranged chronologically by show number.
    - #1, LC Record #95-502768 (Box-folder 628/1)
    - #2, LC Record #95-5033968 (Box-folder 628/2)
    - #3, LC Record #95-503412 (Box-folder 628/3)
    - #4, LC Record #95-503449 (Box-folder 628/4)
    - #5, LC Record #95-503551 (Box-folder 628/5)
    - #6, LC Record #95-503706, #95-503715 (Box-folder 628/6)
    - #7, LC Record #95-503717 (Box-folder 628/7)
    - #8, LC Record #95-503906 (Box-folder 628/8)
    - #9, LC Record #95-503909 (Box-folder 629/1)
    - #10, LC Record #95-503930 (Box-folder 629/2)
    - #11, LC Record #95-504257 (Box-folder 629/3)
    - #12, LC Record #95-504260 (Box-folder 629/4)
    - #13, LC Record #95-504292 (Box-folder 629/5)
    - #14, LC Record #95-504305 (Box-folder 629/6)
    - #15, LC Record #95-504328 (Box-folder 629/7)
    - #16, LC Record #95-504337 (Box-folder 629/8)
    - #17, LC Record #95-504339 (Box-folder 630/1)
    - #18, LC Record #95-504343 (Box-folder 630/2)
    - #19, LC Record #95-504361, #95-504365 (Box-folder 630/3)
    - #20, LC Record #95-504373 (Box-folder 630/4)
    - #21, LC Record #95-504377 (Box-folder 630/5)
    - #22, LC Record #95-504540 (Box-folder 630/6)
    - #23, LC Record #95-504782 (Box-folder 630/7)
    - #24, LC Record #95-504862 (Box-folder 630/8)
    - #25, LC Record #95-505229 (Box-folder 630/9)
    - #26, LC Record #95-505041 (Box-folder 630/10)
    - #27, LC Record #95-505143 (Box-folder 631/1)
    - #28, LC Record #95-505230 (Box-folder 631/2)
    - #29, LC Record #95-505406, #95-505454 (Box-folder 631/3)
    - #30, LC Record #95-505559 (Box-folder 631/4)
    - #31, LC Record #95-505681 (Box-folder 631/5)
    - #32, LC Record #95-505758, #95-506185 (Box-folder 631/6)
    - #33, LC Record #95-506002 (Box-folder 631/7)
    - #34, LC Record #95-506008 (Box-folder 631/8)
    - #35, LC Record #95-506488 (Box-folder 632/1)
    - #36, LC Record #95-506557 (Box-folder 632/2)
    - #37, LC Record #95-506611, #95-507058, #95-507063 (Box-folder 632/3)
    - #38, LC Record #95-507692 (Box-folder 632/4)
    - #39, LC Record #95-507895 (Box-folder 632/5)
    - #40, LC Record #95-508025 (Box-folder 632/6)
    - #41, LC Record #95-508243 (Box-folder 633/1)
    - #42, LC Record #95-508332, #95-508359 (Box-folder 633/2)
    - #43, LC Record #95-508405 (Box-folder 633/3)
    - #44, LC Record #95-508565 (Box-folder 633/4)
    - #45, LC Record #95-508803 (Box-folder 633/5)
    - #46, LC Record #95-508805 (Box-folder 633/6)
    - #47, LC Record #95-508806 (Box-folder 633/7)
    - #48, LC Record #95-508981 (Box-folder 634/1)
    - #49, LC Record #95-508998 (Box-folder 634/2)
    - #50, LC Record #95-509142 (Box-folder 634/3)
    - #51, LC Record #95-509142 (Box-folder 634/4)
    - #52, LC Record #95-509303 (Box-folder 634/5)
    - #53, LC Record #95-509315 (Box-folder 634/6)
    - #54, LC Record #95-509334 (Box-folder 634/7)
    - #55, LC Record #95-509409 (Box-folder 635/1)
    - #56, LC Record #95-509458 (Box-folder 635/2)
    - #57, LC Record #95-509662 (Box-folder 635/3)
    - #58, LC Record #95-509663 (Box-folder 635/4)
    - #59, LC Record #95-509705 (Box-folder 635/5)
    - #60, LC Record #95-509707 (Box-folder 635/6)
    - #61, LC Record #95-509781 (Box-folder 635/7)
    - #62, LC Record #95-509983 (Box-folder 636/1)
    - #63, LC Record #95-510104 (Box-folder 636/2)
    - #64, LC Record #95-510202 (Box-folder 636/3)
    - #65, LC Record #95-510272 (Box-folder 636/4)
    - #66, LC Record #95-510594 (Box-folder 636/5)
    - #67, LC Record #95-510595, #95-510596 (Box-folder 636/6)
    - #68, LC Record #95-510597 (Box-folder 636/7)
    - #69, LC Record #95-510715, #95-510721 (Box-folder 637/1)
    - #70, LC Record #95-510737, #95-510738 (Box-folder 637/2)
    - #71, LC Record #95-510920 (Box-folder 637/3)
    - #72, LC Record #95-510996 (Box-folder 637/4)
    - #73, LC Record #95-510999 (Box-folder 637/5)
    - #74, LC Record #95-511332 (Box-folder 637/6)
    - #75, LC Record #95-511333 (Box-folder 638/1)
    - #76, LC Record #95-511334 (Box-folder 638/2)
    - #77, LC Record #95-5113634 (Box-folder 638/3)
    - #78, LC Record #95-511335 (Box-folder 638/4)
    - #79, LC Record #95-511364 (Box-folder 638/5)
    - #80, LC Record #95-511367 (Box-folder 638/6)
    - #81, LC Record #95-511530 (Box-folder 639/1)
    - #82, LC Record #95-511574 (Box-folder 639/2)